on this Saturday night home at last American war veteran help prisoner by North Korea for more than a month
在这个星期六晚上回家了美国退伍军人帮助囚犯朝鲜为一个多月
85 year old finally free by his captors what's behind deadly freeze
85年老被他俘虏终于自由了什么致命的背后冻结
how much a country founded stranded Airport 2012 power more ice in the forecast
多少钱一个国家创立于预测滞留机场2012电源更多的冰
remembering Mandela we're here in South Africa
记住曼德拉我们在这里在南非
what country celebrates his life Paris to say farewell against apartheid and look behind the most famous photos of Mandela taking the day he was released from prison
哪个国家庆祝他的生命巴黎告别反对种族隔离，看看最有名的照片曼德拉服用当天，他被从监狱中释放的背后
this season NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt reporting tonight from Soweto South Africa
本赛季NBC晚间新闻与莱斯特·霍尔特来自索韦托南非今晚报告
good evening from Soweto industries were so much blood was shed analog and bitter battle against apartheid 352 night Havana place of celebration the life of Nelson Mandela
晚上好从索韦托行业这么多的流血反对种族隔离352夜哈瓦那的地方庆祝模拟和苦战纳尔逊·曼德拉的生活
much more than a few moments what are top stories I come from California 185 year old American man is home after a 7 week or deal as a prisoner in North Korea
超过几分钟什么是顶级的故事我来自加州更185年岁的美国男人是家里7星期后，或处​​理在朝鲜的囚犯
a10 standoff came suddenly the North Korean government saying Merrill Newman a Korean War vet with a heart condition was released for humanitarian reasons NBC's Mike Taibbi is in Palo Alto with more force Michael Vick
A10对峙突然来到朝鲜政府说美林纽曼朝鲜战争的兽医与心脏状况被释放出于人道主义原因NBC的迈克·泰比是在帕洛阿尔托有更多的力量迈克尔·维克
go to the left of the North Korean government says they deported Merrill Newman simply Frida pretension the never should have happened bottom line 85 yr old ex Marine after triple acid much longer than it should have is home
去朝鲜政府的左说，他们被驱逐出境美林纽曼只是弗里达预紧的不该发生的底线85岁老恩海洋三酸后长得比它应该有是家庭
quickly without any prior announcement flight from Hong Kong to Beijing and Merrill Newman finally able to speak freely
很快，恕不另行通知航班从香港到北京和美林纽曼终于能够畅所欲言
then after direct flight to San Francisco American soil to great
再经过直航旧金山美国本土伟大的
who is my family thank you all over
谁是我的家人谢谢大家了
Newman's visit in North Korea organize tour what was pulled office homebound flight on October 26th just minutes before take off and held without explanation
纽曼在朝鲜访问组织旅游什么拉10月26日办公室闲居飞行只需几分钟前起飞，没有解释举行
the elderly man who raise a family in a career in corporate finance the war time record the tune candlelight advisor to Korean anti communist
的老人谁养家的职业生涯在企业融资的战争时间记录调烛光顾问，韩国的反共产主义
the forces during that wore 60 years ago un video de to November 9th North Korean government released an apology that seem to be written for Newman
期间，该部队穿着60年前未视频去到11月9日朝鲜政府发布的，似乎是纽曼书面道歉
and then another full month waiting while back Channel talk to see that the statement from North Korea state news agency taking into consideration Houston shoe repair Torrance is advanced agent health condition the Democratic People's Republic of Korea deported him from the country
然后又是整整一个月等待前阵子频道说话地看到，朝鲜国家通讯社考虑到休斯顿修鞋声明托伦斯先进剂健康状况朝鲜民主主义人民共和国驱逐他从国
what President Joe Biden in South Korea for a memorial on a ring Korean War Dead JD had no role in the negotiations while pressing Newman's release at another American Christian missionary Kenneth Bay still jailed in North Korea
什么总统拜登在韩国圆环上的纪念朝鲜战争死法学博士曾在谈判中没有任何作用，同时按下纽曼的释放在另一位美国基督教传教士丁湾仍关押在朝鲜
should be released
应该被释放
elderly retiree with a heart condition is no home looking forward to kicking back
退休老人与心脏状况是没有家期待踢回
show believed to have in back
节目应该有在回
an end to a visit back in history that was much more than Merrill Newman bar console
结束访问回到历史上比美林纽曼酒吧控制台更
Edwin ass today weather he would ever return to Korea Newman said probably not smile
今天埃德温屁股天气，他会再回到韩国纽曼说大概不会微笑
buy kite in California facts of the United States remains of a group of dangerous and deadly weather tonight making life miserable for millions of people
在美国加州的事实买风筝仍然是一个组危险和致命的天气，今晚让生活苦不堪言以百万计的人
atleast 11 weather related deaths have been reported Weather Channel meteorologist Jim Cantore is watching all this from Dallas forest
ATLEAST 11天气有关的死亡报告天气频道的气象学家吉姆Cantore从达拉斯林看着这一切
Yeah right here the colour of you look at the average temperatures of every spot the country this morning during a particular hour the average temperature was 14 .5 degrees
是啊在这里你的颜色今早某一个小时的平均温度为14 .5度在看每一个点的平均气温在全国
that's colder than any hour of any day all of last winner that cold combine with a boy Ciara has created quite a mess especially in cities like that
这比任何时刻任何一天的寒冷所有最后的赢家，寒冷与一个男孩席亚拉引发了不小的混乱特别是在这样的城市结合
heavy snow ice freezing rain and brutal wins
大雪冰冻雨和残酷胜
lash the central part of the south
睫毛南部的中央部分
Pittsburgh weather system
匹兹堡的天气系统
Dallas and major southern cities temperatures remain below freezing during sleep is the hard iced up to 180 Broadway everyday drives
达拉斯和南部主要城市气温保持在冰点以下睡眠过程中是很难结冰了180百老汇日常驱动器
hundreds of traffic accident reports is Friday causing extensive delays closings 35 chevrolt I'm up to 10 hours to change lanes in your going sideways
数百宗交通意外中是星期五引起广泛的延迟倒闭35 chevrolt我长达10小时变更车道在你去横盘
Ohio is public bus lost control and slams right parked car before sliding down the rest of the road sideways
俄亥俄州是公共巴士失控滑下路的其余部分之前，侧身猛地向右停放的汽车
across Arkansas Texas utility Cruz are scrambling to clear Ison crusted power lines as more than 200
横跨阿肯色得克萨斯公用事业克鲁兹都在争先恐后地清除伊森结痂电源线为200多
remain without power airlines cancel Delia 2012 today with more than half of those wine through Dallas stranding 4000 people OneTravel record this cell phone video of families forced to spend the night at the airport
仍然没有电力航空公司取消迪莉娅2012今天拥有超过这些酒通过达拉斯搁浅4000人OneTravel记录这个手机的家庭录像被迫借宿在机场半
this satellite time lapse shows the size and strength of the storm droppings much is 13 inches of snow in some areas the Arctic airbrush traumatic temperature drops today it was a balmy 81 degrees in Miami
这颗卫星时间的推移显示了风暴的粪便多为13英寸的积雪，部分地区今天的北极喷枪创伤温度下降这是一个温暖的81度在迈阿密的规模和实力
compared with freezing -30 in Havre Montana a difference 111 degrees
用冷冻-30在勒阿弗尔蒙大拿的差别111度相比，
the cold set record lows in Las Vegas in Northern California in the Bay Area for people died from hypothermia a million dollars worth of citrus devastated and now let us an avocado crops are in danger
冷集纪录低点在拉斯维加斯在北加州湾区的人死于体温过低一个价值百万美元的柑橘摧残，现在就让我们一鳄梨作物正处于危险中
back in the East a second storm is putting states like Virginia on high alert for ice the Northeast
早在东第二个风暴是把像弗吉尼亚州处于高度戒备状态的冰东北
let's talk about the second store much is freezing snow in Colerain and about in California it moves out tonight to look at this purple area indicates respect sleeping freezing rain
让我们来谈谈第二家店多是冻结的雪在Colerain以及有关在加州它移出今晚来看看这个紫色区域表示尊重睡觉冻雨
some of the same areas that got the sleep freezing rain from the first or we move into Sunday this Noble in pack cities like Chicago in Omaha Nebraska what is the freezing rain now for Virginia
一些认为有睡眠冻雨从第一或我们进入周日这一崇高包中城市，如芝加哥在内布拉斯加州奥马哈什么是冻雨现为弗吉尼亚同一地区
nation's capital West Virginia Ohio in North Carolina on Monday in tire mess of sleep snow in freezing rain boots right up the i-95 corridor
国家的首都西弗吉尼亚州俄亥俄州北卡罗来纳周一在睡眠雪冻雨靴权利了I-95走廊轮胎一塌糊涂
into the wind frost horrible rush hour in Dallas we stay in the deep freezer until at least Wednesday when we may get above 40
到达拉斯的风霜可怕的高峰时段，我们留在了冰柜，直到至少周三的时候，我们可能会得到40以上
tomorrow is the official day of prayer and reflection here in South Africa part of a 10 day period of mourning over the death of Nelson Mandela behind me the house he once lived in the museum what crowds gathered Rapid a many of them old enough to experience
明天是祈祷和反思在这里的哀悼纳尔逊·曼德拉的死亡在我身后有10天的期限南非部分的正式日子，他曾经住在博物馆什么的人群迅速聚集一个很多人老得足以体验到房子
firsthand the oppression of the white minority government that may have your children here children born into free South Africa ala venta de paying tribute to Mandela and its legacy Richard Engel is also in South Africa has more tonight the current Mandela home Richard
第一手的白人少数政府，可能有你的孩子在这里出生于免费南非阿拉本塔 - 致敬曼德拉和其遗留子女的压迫理查德·恩格尔也是在南非拥有今晚当前曼德拉家理查德
good evening Lester the fighter storm is also rolled into gear in Johannesburg find me the rock 5012 Brookhaven tribute very wet
晚上好莱斯特战斗机风暴也卷进齿轮在约翰内斯堡找到我的磐石5012布鲁克海文国家实验室的敬意很湿
bouquets in front of the homework Nelson Mandela died of South Africans are coming out in celebrating the life of the man who transformed this country
在功课曼德拉去世的南非人面前花束现身庆祝谁改变这个国家的人的生活
no one mourns like
没有人喜欢哀悼
what do women want men and they dance and sing to celebrate the man who helped end apartheid
什么女人希望男人和他们跳舞，唱歌，庆祝谁帮助结束种族隔离的人
the Mandela family also made its first public statement
曼德拉的家人也进行了首次公开声明
is the feminine woodland from him leprosy Avenged was that made him to me that that was a nice b***
从他的女性化林地麻风报复的是，让他对我说，这是一个不错的b ***
24 month lease is the lesson about that life lived for others is the life well lived
24个月租赁是关于生命的教训为别人活着就是良好的生活
in Johannesburg Mandela Square they came to take pictures by is message that you make me proud
在约翰内斯堡曼德拉广场，他们来到了拍照者是消息，你让我骄傲
sign your name does books in Lake Worth
签上你的名字呢书籍雷克沃思
you need to go to quarts
你需要去夸脱
because I wanted him to get understanding of the pics of
因为我想他得到的图片的理解
the human bean did Nelson Mandela was
人类豆做了纳尔逊·曼德拉是
victims of apartheid children who grew up free application
儿童种族隔离受害者谁长大的免费应用程序
Becky mother brought his 17-year-old are the Mandela Center for memory Museum of his life and struggle
贝基的母亲带着他17岁的曼德拉中心为他的生活和斗争记忆博物馆
from his letters in meat and tiny handwriting to smoke out of prison
从他的肉和微小的手写抽烟走出监狱的信件
the highlights of the Nobel Prize
诺贝尔奖的亮点
the resistance glasses replica Mandela's cell text just three small steps to cross for years Mandela to deliver a baby in here just a map on a concrete floor
阻力眼镜复制品曼德拉的单元格的文本只是三个小步骤，穿越多年曼德拉在这里提供一个宝宝刚一在水泥地上地图
roll the celebration of anxiety here Nelson Mandela the nation's most famous Sun is coming father the question what would be like without
滚焦虑的庆祝活动在这里纳尔逊·曼德拉全国最有名的太阳来了父亲的问题会是什么不一样
tomorrow that day of prayer for when a massive Memorial and finally the burial a self certificate back to be wet all week
明天祈祷的日子，当一个巨大的纪念碑，最后埋葬自我证书回到一周都湿
Richard Engel in Johannesburg crime and Ally have been in prison 13 years when high school students parents to 101 to protest against apartheid government
理查德·恩格尔在约翰内斯堡犯罪和盟友已经在监狱里13年当高中学生家长101，抗议种族隔离政府
Mellow Man Delaware remain in prison other 14 years of protest mark a turning point for change the countries Direction onesie Nature Boy iconic photo became symbols of a need for change
醇厚的男人特拉华留在监狱里的其他14年抗议标志着一个转折点，改变国家的方向连身衣大自然男孩标志性的照片成为了一个需要改变的符号
free young girlies Antoinette Peterson the bloodied and lifeless boy in the arms of a stranger is a 13 year old brother Hector it was June 16 1976 the day this a 100 uprising began
免费年轻girlies安托瓦内特彼得森在一个陌生人的怀抱血淋淋的，毫无生气的男孩是一个13岁的弟弟赫克托这是1976年6月16日的一天，这个100起义开始
NW plus minus
净重正负
can u mass index number raining on Monday
可以在周一ü质量指数下雨
began as a peaceful protest by high school students against a government policy requiring them to learn in African language of the white minority government
一开始是由高中学生反对政府的政策，要求他们学会在少数白人政府的非洲语言中的和平抗议
student visa message but you have no idea that you were in danger how much does a message
学生签证的消息，但你不知道，你是在危险有多大呢留言
but then tear gas followed by bullets were fired at the crown by police scores including young Hector it wasn't even supposed to be there were killed at first a
但随后催泪弹其次是子弹射向冠被警察成绩，包括年轻的赫克托它甚至不应该在那里起初被打死
p******* no p**** myself on the Ave and crazy knex moment does indeed
p *******无P ****自己的大道和疯狂KNEX时刻确确
the March between a pricing and a seminal moment to the battle against apartheid
定价和一个开创性的时刻，以反对种族隔离的战斗之间的三月
there is a permanent marker on the corner were Hector Peterson dodge just outside the school
有对角永久性标记是赫克托皮特森轻功只是外校
it was no coincidences student uprising beginning this part of Soweto it's just a few blocks amor Nelson Mandela lip and now he was in prison at the time huge influence in this neighborhood is life story serve as a call to action
这是没有巧合的学生起义开始这部分索韦托的，它只是几个街区阿莫尔纳尔逊·曼德拉的嘴唇，现在他在监狱里在这附近的时候巨大的影响是终生的故事作为一个呼吁采取行动
things to uprising because of you because we know that the City soulmates you
事情，因为你要起义，因为我们知道，市知音你
why I was sleeping and 42 something
为什么我正在睡觉，42的东西
the uprising with claim hundreds of lives before it was over what does a severely damaged
权利要求数百人的生命起义之前，它是在什么是一个严重受损
apartheid government and rally world opinion against it
种族隔离政府和拉力世界舆论反对
I don't self interested in Africa that lives in peas and rice Rachael hominy
我不关心自身在非洲，生活在豌豆和大米瑞秋霍米尼
and auto biting commitment a piece of grilled order
和自动咬承诺一块烤订单
what days the weather high school students to young to have known life under apartheid visit the Hector Peterson memorial it was not the current generation struggle but it is their history
什么几天天气高中生年轻，知道生活在种族隔离制度下参观赫克托皮特森纪念它不是目前这一代的斗争却是他们的历史
The Beacon forget about it
烽火台忘掉它
text to David and get over in about anything else do you think that getting better
文本大卫和克服在其它任何东西，你认为渐入佳境
Testament the legacy of a young boy and a bill a liter
约的一个小男孩的传统和一项法案一升
Nelson Nelson Mandela was on her with a statue of an iconic Hector Peterson photo back in 2006 in Hawaii 2013 Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor
纳尔逊·曼德拉是在她的一个标志性的赫克托皮特森照片雕像早在2006年在夏威夷珍珠港2013日本偷袭
what happened 72 years ago today launch the United States into World War 2 attending today
发生了什么事72年年前的今天今天推出美国进入第二次世界大战出席
ceremonies for 50 survivors of the attack feel more than 2400 merican early morning in Hawaii
仪式50幸存者的攻击感觉比2400 merican清晨在夏威夷
97.wav
what is continuous on this Saturday of pollution emergency the world's most populous city
什么是连续污染应急世界上人口最多的城市这个星期六
what surprising is where the Samaritan
什么令人惊讶的是，其中撒玛利亚
health emergency tonight in Shanghai Chinese city with more than 70 million people think of the worst air pollution is ever seen a report tonight mendeecees in Williams
卫生应急今晚在上海的中国城市拥有超过7000万人次认为空气污染最严重的是见过的报告今晚mendeecees威廉斯
the Soaring skyline of mainland Chinese commercial capital building a smudge stick Smaug the tallest buildings disappear into the smoke mini in the City wedding mosques
大陆中国商业资本建设涂抹棒史矛革最高的建筑物消失在烟雾mini在城市结婚清真寺的翱翔天际
I have difficulty in breathing 624 euros way to you is ability to Lose a bad and says my mood its been a week of stately rising record pollution levels in Shanghai is it from to the highest level of health warning
我有呼吸困难624欧元的方式给你的是失去一个坏的能力，并说我的心情了一个星期的庄严记录污染水平在上海崛起是从健康警告的最高水平
the concentration of the most dangerous particles in 20 times what will help you can I say s*** in regards as hazardous I didn't think it's good for humans to living this kind of environment says this man
这名男子在20倍最危险的粒子怎样才能帮助你，我可以说S ***的问候为危险我不认为这是很好的适合人类居住的这种环境的浓度称
hundreds of flights were cancelled delayed schools closed Presidents search to stay in tools in factories of the couple stop production
数百个航班被取消延迟关闭学校校长搜索留在工具中的情侣停止生产工厂
30 percent of government vehicles will the roads ships pulls to navigate Corsa C through the Hayes explain the cold wind blows weather for cloud of pollution from cars factories in coal-burning is Santa in China for most of the week
政府车辆的30％将道路船拉来浏览可赛C到海耶斯解释的寒风吹来天气的云污染来自于燃煤汽车工厂是圣诞老人在中国大多数的一周
is the record-breaking levels in other cities included in Beijing DCF
在其他城市的破纪录的水平包括在北京的DCF
the government is announced many plans to fight the pollution parent progress
政府宣布许多计划打造成污染的父进程
smokin eastern China restarting to live today but its starting to approach hazardous levels the east and north of China River humble in winter just getting into the coldest month
斯莫中国东部重启今天的生活，但它的起点接近危险水平中国河在冬季的东部和北部谦虚刚刚进入最冷的月份
Williams NBC News Beijing
威廉姆斯NBC新闻北京
the results are in tonight after another conversation we've been falling involving a young American woman who made it to the very end top 30 most unlikely contest NBC's Duncan golestani was watching it all in Beirut
结果今晚在另一次谈话，我们一直下降，涉及一名年轻的美国女人谁做的很后结束前30位最不可能的较量NBC的邓肯golestani看着这一切在贝鲁特
tonight 12218 happy just to the finals
今晚12218高兴了总决赛
Jennifer Sultan RS notice you speak Arabic that was played when she first audition
珍妮弗苏丹RS注意到你讲阿拉伯语的被演奏，当她第一次试镜
what's your name Jennifer
你叫什么名字Jennifer
what's the score against law to Jennifer
什么是对法律詹妮弗比分
backstage this week to 23 year old music right told me she fell in love in college improvising learning songs
后台本周23岁的音乐权利告诉我，她爱上了在大学学习即兴歌曲